Little cuts everywhere
The blade dressed up polite
You left a bit loud
But the timing ain't right, I checked
Said maybe it's me, that is don't lie
They repeat like a bee
Info late then call it a nine
You're playing chess while it did
I redesigned
Wanna know is I gave you none
Now you're wondering what I become
Eyes don't feel it shift
But you can't get confidence starting to bomb
You needed heat, I dropped a degree
I have a few messages to throw out here.
First of all, let me teach you guys a trick.
And I guess Alexandre determined to do this trick really well.
So if you want to just play stupid games with people, you know, give them a few, a few more
and pull the rug out from under them, and then when they say, well, what did I do or what happened,
don't even give them the courtesy of a response. Just make a bunch of accusations, you know, just
bullshit, and then say, well, you know what you did. Would that get in my mind all spinning? What
did I do? What did I do? I didn't do shit to you. I didn't ask you for anything. All I did was be nice
I specifically was like, I'm just gonna give this person love.
I'm not even gonna have them question it
because they're paranoid persons.
I'm just gonna give them love.
You're gonna do that to me.
And you say, I did something to you.
And okay, careless cunt, or sorry, clueless cunt.
Not you, I'm talking to careless Kate now.
Careless Kate.
So someone said something about some midget in your family.
I don't even know about it.
Oh my god, how dare you?
And then you go on to like post, I got like 20, 30 photos of me,
they got manipulated, photos of my cats manipulated,
calling me an abuser of animals and stuff
and a predator protector or whatever.
Bitch, okay, okay, let's have a little contest.
You get my mug shots and then I'll get your mug shots
and we'll see who looks fatter in them.
Oh, okay, already that's obvious, I will lose that.
You fat pig. Okay, first of all, but I have your bunk shots.
You look skinnier than you do now.
You look okay, you look decent on them.
Must have done all the math, right?
But, you wanna play with me, you fucking bitch?
You wanna play with me?
Mmm, keep playing.
Okay, Tiny Tim won't have a Christmas, okay?
You dumb bitch.
Ugh.
I mean, god, every day I have to wake up.
Oh, look at, look at Psycho here or, you know, Cyrax or Psycho.
Oh, here he is holding his cat, and the cats are so unhappy.
Like, I have to show, I mean, you see,
I only see like 25 hours a day where they're always by me.
They love me.
If they're not, you don't understand cats,
you're just a dumb cunt, you're just so dumb.
You know, it's not like you're a dumb dog.
You can actually pick up cats, and if they don't like it,
they'll like, you know, leave your arms,
but they don't even need to.
I just put them down.
Oh, and, oh, I can't, oh, but Sweet Pea, oh, Sweet Pea,
are you, I mean, it's like Sweet Pea's just as bad as you.
Dumber than you, for sure.
Oh, and it's making fun of me using AI and like Sweet Pea
and you, look at the Sweet Pea and you.
You're not Darcy from 90 Day Fiancé,
I know you wish you were.
You look like Darcy's ass, okay?
There you go, both of you, you fat pigs.
So how's everyone else?
Hope everyone's good.
Everyone's being silent. I hate you. I mean, it's like, I'm getting so sick of this. I'm just gonna like fucking like
They're gonna sit here. I mean, is there anybody like real anymore?
It's much of fat
Stupid bitches not not most of you in the chat, but I mean people that are fucking like
That's the thing to say just just go away
Just sit here in a stair, and then you say, oh
You're like the most of the audience you see you're like a bunch of lumps so sick of this shit
develop a personality maybe then I will I'm just gonna go on strike until it
happens and personality kind of character jeez I have to do everything
around here right
If you care, join the tribe with me on flares
Echoes of funky bass and beat
Oh, while sermon can't be beat
Step by step, let's break the mold
In this left, let's enjoy
Hands up, shout it out
We're the one